<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Open Source Development Blog</title>
    <link>http://osdlabs.github.io/blog/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on Open Source Development Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2017</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 12:26:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://osdlabs.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Mission Statement</title>
      <link>http://osdlabs.github.io/blog/post/mission-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2017 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://osdlabs.github.io/blog/post/mission-statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hey guys! We&amp;rsquo;re all really excited about our first blog post.
In this one, we&amp;rsquo;d like to elaborate on what OSDLabs stands to do and how &lt;em&gt;you&lt;/em&gt; can be a part of it. For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know, Open Source Development Labs is an initiative to bring Open Source innovation to campus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have always believed in sharing code and building better software. &lt;strong&gt;Period&lt;/strong&gt;. This is what &amp;lsquo;Open Source&amp;rsquo; fundamentally means. To freely collaborate and code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, this can only be done when everyone comes together with the best of intentions to bring out something significant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shouldn’t campus software be written by students?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Shouldn’t we be pursuing cool projects to make our lives easier?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;ve always felt you&amp;rsquo;d like to be a part of something bigger in the grand scale of things, this is the right place for you. We are setting out to nurture a community where students &lt;strong&gt;tinker&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;hack&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;design&lt;/strong&gt; together.
The diverse thoughts, ideas and methodologies flying around, inherently set up a great environment for innovation.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be alarmed by your capabilities. &lt;em&gt;Anyone&lt;/em&gt; with a skillset can contribute to OSDLabs. We will be hosting more educational sessions over the semester as you get to explore domains and find your interests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Campus infrastructure developments require the faculty and students to bring about disruptive change &lt;strong&gt;together&lt;/strong&gt;. We are in plans to set up this ‘seamless’ process, a flexible system where people easily take up interesting projects and hack away. You will get the opportunity to work under experienced mentors and gain exposure while committing to fruitful work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more developments as we will be releasing some pretty exciting stuff in the coming weeks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any queries in mind or would simply like to discuss an idea, feel free to message us on our Slack &lt;a href=&#34;http://bitsgoacodes.slack.com/signup&#34;&gt;channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>